Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
Edwin Diamond Political Audiovisual Collection
- Tapes D0900-D1199
  - D1177 Politics and Television: A Look at the MIT Cable television System, 12/19/77 (Box 47)
  - D1178 Politics and Television: A Look at the MIT Cable television System, 12/19/77 (Box 47)
  - D1179 Guest Lectures vs. The World, 12/1/78 (Box 47)
  - D1180 White Timilty TV Spots, 1975/1979 (Box 47)
  - D1181 Bush - Reagan, 4/24/80 (Box 47)
  - D1182 The Boys on the Bus '80 - The Godfather, 6/6/80 (Box 47)
  - D1183 Ford's Inauguration, Highlights of Nixon Farewell to Staff (Box 47)
  - D1184 Political Commercials, Assorted 1964 - 70, '60 Nixon Lodge, '60 Kennedy, '64 Johnson, '64 Goldwater, '68 Humphrey, '68 Nixon (Box 47)
  - D1185 Kennedy, Nixon '60, Agnew, others, Reagan, McGovern (Box 47)
  - D1186 Pres. Candidates, Scoop Jackson, George Wallace, Ronald Reagan / CBS '75 Review, 1976 (Box 47)
  - D1187 University of Michigan - Coverage of Election '72 for Major Networks - Reel 1 (Box 47)
  - D1188 University of Michigan Coverage '72 of Major Networks - Reel 2 of Election (Box 47)
  - D1189 Arsenic and Old Lace (Box 47)
  - D1190 Arsenic and Old Lace, Empty case no tape (Box 47)
  - D1191 Middle East - Camp David Agreement / Carter Presentation to Congress / CBS Analysis of Speech (Box 47)
  - D1192 Mike Taibbi, Jack Cole, other TV people, MIT (Box 47)
  - D1193 NH - Nordheimer / Udall (Box 47)
  - D1194 ADS - Full Tape / Gaan & Martin "Just Another Weapon" (Box 47)
  - D1195 NH Cole - Broder - Schneider (Box 47)
  - D1196 Japanese Programs III (Box 48)
  - D1197 Political Commercials (White Timilty) (Box 48)
  - D1198 MASS '78 Hatch, King, Tsongas (Box 48)
  - D1199 Anti Busing Rally - Southie Parade (Part I) (Box 48)
- Tapes D1200-D1259
  - D1200 Anti Busing Rally - Southie Parade (Part II) (Box 48)
  - D1201 The Role of Television in Nixon's Political Career (Box 48)
  - D1202 Boston Globe Covers the '76 Election - Interview with Curtis Wilkie (Box 48)
  - D1203 Women in Advertising Afternoon vs Evening (Box 48)
  - D1204 Ford on the News - White at Mayor's Conference - Regan, ?, Kennedy, Church Shots - Watergate (Box 48)
  - D1205 TVTV Gerald Ford's America I) Win II) Chic to Sheik (Box 48)
  - D1206 TV Advertising: "The Cat That Barked" / Interview with Jerry Della Femina (Box 48)
  - D1207 Day Commercials vs Night Commercials (Box 48)
  - D1208 Advertisements / Class Discussion - Marc Anderson, Dave Maurer, George Hays (Box 48)
  - D1209 Interview Outtakes from L. Dyatt & J. Margulis (Box 48)
  - D1210 Working Tape (Box 48)
  - D1211 Energy: Interviews w/Public on Carter's Policy (Box 48)
  - D1212 Be Yourself: Commercial Spots (Box 48)
  - D1213 Freedom House Interview (Drug Rehab) Pro - Busing (Box 48)
  - D1214 Desegregation Coverage winter 1976, Local Channels, Interviews, News, Features (Box 48)
  - D1215 Political Ads: Carter, Harris, Reagan, McCormack, Harris, Ch. 4 Candidate Overview, Jackson (Box 48)
  - D1216 Assorted Political Spots (Box 48)
  - D1217 Play It Again, Sam - Woody Allen, Diane Keaton (Box 48)
  - D1218 Ads - Full Tape (Box 48)
  - D1219 NH Election Night (Box 48)
  - D1220 NH Carter Interviews, Cassie Mackew, Foreign Television Crews (Box 48)
  - D1221 Behind the Lines: Free Press Fair Trial - Nixon and the Press (Box 48)
  - D1222 1987 Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race Campaign Spots - Edward King, Frank Hatch (Box 48)
  - D1223 Nixon and Opponents (Box 48)
  - D1224 Kennedy for Tsongas / Bellotti (Box 48)
  - D1225 1976 Political Spots - Carter, Reagan, Udall, Jackson, Harris, Bayh, McCormack, Church, Wallace, Ford, Humphrey (Box 49)
  - D1226 Interview - Bill Aber (Box 49)
  - D1227 Interview...Investigate [label torn] (Box 49)
  - D1228 Hyde Park, Charlestown / Interview with Gary Armstrong / Coverage of Busing Coverage (Box 49)
  - D1229 2d Kennedy/Nixon Debate - Part 1 of 2 (Box 49)
  - D1230 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1231 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1232 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1233 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1234 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1235 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1236 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1237 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1238 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1239 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1240 unlabeled (Box 49)
  - D1241 case with reel but no film (unlabelled) (Box 49)
  - D1242 PSA Moral (Pro - Choice) 1979 - Producer: 17.24 Project (Box 50)
    1/4 inch audio tape
  - D1243 Bio, Basics, Accomplishments - Producer: Clyde See for Governor (Box 50)
  - D1244 4 Radio Spots - Producer: Les Apsen for Congress, 10/12/84 (Box 50)
  - D1245 Nixon Radio Spots - Russia #1, Youth Rally, Record #2, Nixon Doctrine, Drugs - Producer: The November Group, 9/14/72 (Box 50)
  - D1246 Music, Hunter - Producer: See for Governor, 10/18/84 (Box 50)
  - D1247 Cash Jingle - Producer: West Virginia Democratic Committee (Box 50)
  - D1248 Phil Sharp Radio - Rates - Producer: William Morgan Co., 10/9/84 (Box 50)
  - D1249 Republicans in Congress - 3 - Spots - Producer: Winkler Video Associates (Box 50)
  - D1250 Political Science Class, 10/13/71 (Box 50)
  - D1251 Political Science Lecture - Edwin Diamond, 10/20/71 (Box 50)
  - D1252 Political Science Lecture - Edwin Diamond, 10/27/71 (Box 50)
  - D1253 Political Science Lecture - Edwin Diamond, 11/1/71 (Box 50)
  - D1254 Political Science Lecture - Edwin Diamond, 11/17/71 (Box 50)
  - D1255 17.24 Lecture, 12/8/71 (Box 50)
  - D1256 Political Science Class, 12/15/71 (Box 50)
  - D1257 McGovern Radio Spots 11972 (Box 50)
  - D1258 Sloan Meeting With Owens, Cantor, 'Off Campus Experiment' (Box 50)
  - D1259 Who Owns the Air? (Box 50)
- Films D1260-D1270
  - D1260 Too Much to Drink (National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism), diamond_e_001; Film: 16mm (Oversize 1)
  - D1261 Computer (Ogilvy and Mather: Smith Barney), 4/16/1981; diamond_e_007; Film: 16mm (Oversize 2)
  - D1262 Nursery (Ogilvy and Mather: Smith Barney), diamond_e_006; Film: 16mm (Oversize 2)
  - D1263 Roller Coaster (Ogilvy and Mather: Smith Barney), diamond_e_004; Film: 16mm (Oversize 1)
  - D1264 Space Shuttle (Ogilvy and Mather: Smith Barney), diamond_e_002; Film: 16mm (Oversize 1)
  - D1265 Amphitheater (Smith Barney), diamond_e_003; Film: 16mm (Oversize 1)
  - D1266 Fisherman (Smith Barney), diamond_e_005; Film: 16mm (Oversize 2)
  - D1268 Follow the Leader: Young Republicans National Convention (Roll 2) Friday Afternoon Balloting June 25-28, 1963, Jun 1963; diamond_e_012; Notes in can read: "Roll II - Friday afternoon balloting - noise - Lukens victory speech - shaking hands with Chuck Knowland [?]"; Film: 16mm (Oversize 1)
  - D1270 Follow the Leader: Young Republicans National Convention (Roll 3) ) Sound for Roll 5, Jun 1963; diamond_e_011; Notes in can read: "Roll III - partial sound track for Roll IV - appears black at begining"; Film: 16mm (Oversize 3)
  - D1269 Follow the Leader: Young Republicans National Convention (Roll 4), Jun 1963; diamond_e_008; Notes in can read: "Roll 4 - Negative of early morning Thurs. June 27 and Lukens, McDevitt press conf. Duplicate of Roll I and II - sound track."; Film: 16mm; running time 25:00 (Oversize 2)
  - D1270 Follow the Leader: Young Republicans National Convention (Roll 5) Entire Friday Proceedings Goldwater Rally, Jun 1963; diamond_e_010; Notes in can read: "Roll V - negative uncut entire Friday proceedings"; Film: 16mm (Oversize 3)
  - D1269 Follow the Leader: Young Republicans National Convention (Roll 6), Jun 1963; diamond_e_009; Notes in can read: "Roll VI - sound track but needs researching."; Film: 16mm; running time 20:00 (Oversize 2)
  - D1267 Follow the Leader: Young Republicans National Convention (Roll 7) Audio Reel, Jun 1963; diamond_e_013; Notes in can read: "VII - Sound - Gaston - Goldwater rally - speech - Gaston stays in race - floor fight credentials argument Calif - Goldwater rally and speech - New Jersey credentials fight - final take on [?] - pix on Roll V - Interviews at end of Roll V"; Film: 16mm (Oversize 1)
  - D1271 Bounty - Challenger / Thrill - K Lesson (missing as of 3/28/2008)
    16mm
  - D1272 P5-335 National Guard (missing as of 3/28/2008)
  - D1273 [unlabeled] (missing as of 3/28/2008)